around a hundred thousand cyclists
joined the recent prudential ride in
london and our very own correspondent
bim Santos joined the Philippine team as
they navigated around the historic city
and the nearby countryside let's watch
this it is dubbed as the world's largest
cycling festival the seventh staging the
Prudential right London saw the streets
of the storied city posting an estimated
100,000 cyclists cyclists of all stripes
professional to enthusiasts the
commuters took part in the two day event
on August 3 - for Dan'l event aims to
reach a same level of prestige as
London's other marquee sporting events
such as the London Marathon and
Wimbledon and each year different
activities is making this event is for
everybody and it's about helping people
to control of their fitness have a great
time
but most importantly raise money for
good causes over 900 charities each year
benefits around the world from
Prudential Ride London
potential life Philippines feel that its
own contingent composed of his three
celebrity ambassadors namely cavity Anza
Gretchen Ho and Zoran Legaspi
yours truly was also included in the
Philippine team during the survey 100
miler which was created as a legacy
event of the 2012 Olympic Games the
route talked cyclists from close off to
the streets in London
starting at the Queen Elizabeth Park all
around a Dilla countryside of Surry
County in southeast England second aid
station
our third 37-point 96 Mouse the story
100 rod finishes at the mall our load in
central London : read that leads to the
Buckingham Palace despite some usual
hiccups event was a success the
Prudential rod London team is hoping
that the donations collected this year
will at least match the record thirteen
million pounds race last year
AHA that will hopefully set the stage
for a bigger goal next year being Santos
we are one news